hi this video explains when it's a great
idea to use the spotlight tour element
in an onboarding experience it's a clip
from a launch event video for 2023
release Wave 2 but it's equally relevant
today let's turn it over to Sarah who'll
tell us more about
it so as s showed Spotlight tours are a
really powerful way of showing some of
the key selling points in business
Central such as teams and Excel and the
super power of this pattern is really um
that it allows users not only to
discover it but actually go and try it
out with just two steps and hopefully
get
wowed at the moment Spotlight tours are
all about teams and Excel what is up to
you to decide is on which Pages you want
to call out that particular
feature in case it's relevant on the
page Pages you have
built you can use the introduction text
on the first step to explain the value
it brings on that particular page and
remember when you're at a new place it's
sometimes a little difficult to know
where you are so give a little hand
there and introduce where you are the
Second Step it's all about it's it's
about pointing uh to that action where
the user can go and try it out to learn
more visit aka. ms/ BC onboarding thank
you for watching
[Music]